<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Okkei Patcher</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="okkei">Okkei</string>
  <string name="patch">Patch</string>
  <string name="unpatch">Unpatch</string>
  <string name="clear_data">Clear all data</string>
  <string name="savedata_checkbox">Backup/restore save data</string>
  <string name="dialog_ok">OK</string>
  <string name="dialog_exit">Exit</string>
  <string name="dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="dialog_update">Update</string>
  <string name="abort">Abort</string>
  <string name="error">Error</string>
  <string name="attention">Attention</string>
  <string name="warning">Warning</string>
  <string name="exception">Exception</string>
  <string name="patch_success">Patched successfully.</string>
  <string name="unpatch_success">Restored successfully.</string>
  <string name="aborted">Operation aborted.</string>
  <string name="data_cleared">All data cleared.</string>
  <string name="no_install_permission">Okkei Patcher can\'t get permission to install packages.</string>
  <string name="no_storage_permission">Okkei Patcher can\'t get permission to read from and write to external storage.</string>
  <string name="no_storage_permission_rationale">Okkei Patcher requires permission to read from and write to external storage to proceed. Would you like to try to grant permission again? Otherwise Okkei Patcher will be closed.</string>
  <string name="no_storage_permission_settings">Okkei Patcher requires permission to read from and write to external storage to proceed. Would you like to try to grant permission again? If you click OK you will be redirected to Okkei Patcher settings where you should go to permissions settings and enable storage permission. Otherwise Okkei Patcher will be closed.</string>
  <string name="unknown_sources_notice">Okkei Patcher requires permission to install applications from unknown sources to continue. After pressing the OK button you will be redirected to your device settings where you should enable this option. Then you can return to Okkei Patcher using the back button or gesture.</string>
  <string name="long_process_warning">This process can take quite a long time. If you abort it or close Okkei Patcher your CHAOS;CHILD installation and/or Okkei Patcher data may be damaged. Are you sure you want to start the process?</string>
  <string name="clear_data_warning">You\'re about to clear ALL Okkei Patcher data including backup of your old CHAOS;CHILD installation. Use this ONLY when reinstalling CHAOS;CHILD because of data damage. This operation cannot be undone. Are you sure you want to clear all data?</string>
  <string name="abort_warning">Are you sure you want to abort the process? Your CHAOS;CHILD installation and/or Okkei Patcher data may be damaged.</string>
  <string name="download_size_warning">You\'re about to download %1$s MB of data. Ensure that you have stable internet connection. We recommend to use Wi-Fi instead of mobile data.</string>
  <string name="install_prompt_patch">You will now be prompted to install patched CHAOS;CHILD. Please confirm the installation.</string>
  <string name="install_prompt_unpatch">You will now be prompted to install original unmodified CHAOS;CHILD. Please confirm the installation.</string>
  <string name="uninstall_prompt_patch">You will now be prompted to uninstall unmodified CHAOS;CHILD. Please confirm the uninstallation.</string>
  <string name="uninstall_prompt_unpatch">You will now be prompted to uninstall patched CHAOS;CHILD. Please confirm the uninstallation.</string>
  <string name="restore_old_saves">Restoring old save data...</string>
  <string name="compare_obb">Comparing OBB checksums...</string>
  <string name="compare_saves">Comparing save data checksums...</string>
  <string name="compare_apk">Comparing APK checksums...</string>
  <string name="compare_scripts">Comparing scripts checksums...</string>
  <string name="backup_saves">Backuping save data...</string>
  <string name="backup_obb">Backuping OBB...</string>
  <string name="backup_apk">Backuping APK...</string>
  <string name="download_obb">Downloading OBB...</string>
  <string name="download_scripts">Downloading scripts...</string>
  <string name="copy_apk">Copying APK...</string>
  <string name="extract_scripts">Extracting scripts...</string>
  <string name="replace_scripts">Replacing scripts...</string>
  <string name="sign_apk">Signing APK...</string>
  <string name="installing">Installing...</string>
  <string name="write_obb_md5">Writing OBB checksum...</string>
  <string name="write_saves_md5">Writing save data checksum...</string>
  <string name="write_apk_md5">Writing APK checksum...</string>
  <string name="write_patched_apk_md5">Writing patched APK checksum...</string>
  <string name="write_scripts_md5">Writing scripts checksum...</string>
  <string name="saves_not_found_patch">Save data was not found. Okkei Patcher can not perform backup of your current save data and will continue patching process.</string>
  <string name="saves_not_found_unpatch">Save data was not found. Okkei Patcher can not perform backup of your current save data and will continue restoring process.</string>
  <string name="obb_not_found_patch">OBB file was not found. Okkei Patcher will abort patching process.</string>
  <string name="obb_not_found_unpatch">Backup of OBB file was not found. Okkei Patcher will abort restoring process.</string>
  <string name="checking">Checking...</string>
  <string name="restore_obb">Restoring OBB...</string>
  <string name="restore_saves">Restoring save data...</string>
  <string name="saves_backup_not_found">Save data backup was not found. Okkei Patcher can not restore your old save data.</string>
  <string name="error_patched">CHAOS;CHILD is already patched.</string>
  <string name="error_not_patched">CHAOS;CHILD hasn\'t been patched yet.</string>
  <string name="cc_not_found">CHAOS;CHILD was not found on this device.</string>
  <string name="backup_not_found">Backup of CHAOS;CHILD was not found.</string>
  <string name="no_free_space_patch">Not enough free disk space. Ensure that you have at least 2 GB for a backup.</string>
  <string name="no_free_space_unpatch">Not enough free disk space. Ensure that you have at least 2 GB to restore your backup.</string>
  <string name="install_error">An error occurred while installing APK. Please try again.</string>
  <string name="uninstall_error">CHAOS;CHILD was not uninstalled. Please try again.</string>
  <string name="not_trustworthy_apk_patch">APK to be installed might be not created by Okkei Patcher. Please restart patching process.</string>
  <string name="not_trustworthy_apk_unpatch">APK to be installed might be not created by Okkei Patcher. Okkei Patcher will now abort restoring process.</string>
  <string name="apk_not_found_patch">APK to be installed was not found. Please restart patching process.</string>
  <string name="apk_not_found_unpatch">APK to be installed was not found. Okkei Patcher will now abort restoring process.</string>
  <string name="http_file_access_error">Failed to access a file to download. Contact the creator of this application.&#10;Error description: %1$s</string>
  <string name="http_file_download_error">An error occurred while downloading file. Check your internet connection and try again.</string>
  <string name="exception_notice">Send \"bugreport.log\" file located in OkkeiPatcher directory to the creator of this application.</string>
  <string name="fab_version">Version %1$s by solru</string>
  <string name="manifest_prompt">For proper work Okkei Patcher needs an internet connection to download data about patch and updates. Before you proceed by clicking OK ensure that you have stable internet connection.</string>
  <string name="manifest_download">Downloading manifest...</string>
  <string name="manifest_download_completed">Manifest downloaded.</string>
  <string name="manifest_download_aborted">Manifest download aborted. Okkei Patcher can't proceed. Please restart Okkei Patcher.</string>
  <string name="manifest_corrupted">Manifest is corrupted. Okkei Patcher can't proceed. Please try to restart Okkei Patcher.</string>
  <string name="hash_obb_mismatch">Downloaded OBB is corrupted. Please try restarting patch process again.</string>
  <string name="hash_scripts_mismatch">Downloaded scripts are corrupted. Please try restarting patch process again.</string>
  <string name="update_header">Update</string>
  <string name="update_app_available">A new version of Okkei Patcher is available!\nDownload size: %1$s MB\nChangelog:\n%2$s</string>
  <string name="update_app_download">Downloading update...</string>
  <string name="update_app_aborted">Okkei Patcher update was canceled.</string>
  <string name="update_app_corrupted">Okkei Patcher update is corrupted. Try again later.</string>
  <string name="update_app_attention">You will now be prompted to install updated Okkei Patcher. Please confirm the installation. Note that after that Okkei Patcher will be closed and you'll have to relaunch it manually.</string>
  <string name="update_patch_available">Patch update is available! Click PATCH button to download and apply the update.\nDownload size: %1$s MB</string>
</resources>